BOTIRJON ERGASHOV

BACKEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+998-99-590-78-50

ergashovbotirjon4@gmail.com

talantblog.herokuapp.com

44 2-4 Yashnabad d. Tashkent city

SKILLS

Web Developer

Backend developer

TelegramBot

Desktop developer

EDUCATION

Telecommunication

Tashkent University of Information Texnology

2019-now

Faculty of Telecommunication Technologies

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE

HTML/CSS/JS ♦ ♦ ♦ ♦

TelegramBot



English



PROFILE

I am Botirjon Ergashov. I was born on November 6, 1999 in Bulung'ur district of Samarkand region. I have been doing programming for more than 3 years. I have been working with C++ for 1 year, Python for 0.5 years, Frontend for 0.5 years and Django Backend for more than 1.5 years. I've done many small and large projects with Django.

EXPERIENCE

Python Backend course

FulFil Team 2021-2022

- Online course on Python programming language. The duration is 4 months.
- Telegram bot . Telegrambot making use Python Aiogram library. The duration is 2 months.
- A course on making a website backend in Python with the Django Framework.
 The duration is 4 months.
- Publish an API with the Django Rest Framework and enable API usage in other programming languages. The duration is 2 months.

SELF-STUDY

2019-2022

- I learned the C++ programming language courses at the university..
- Data Structure and Database.
- Web frontend (HTML/CSS/JavaScript) courses CODELIBER online course.
- · Lots of YouTube courses on the Django backend.
- Finding the best solution to many programming problems.
- Full site development, API release and online upload skills.

Experiments and projects

2020-2022

Web Sites:

- talantblog.herokuapp.com/
- metsenatapi.herokuapp.com/api/
- · talantecommerse.herokuapp.com
- calm-reef-55003.herokuapp.com

TelegramBots:

- @Imkon_uzbek_bot
- @TvaSQlbot
- @kompyuter_arxitekturasibot
- @kompyuter_arxitekturasibot

Github profile: github.com/TalandBotirjon
Leetcode profile: leetcode.com/ergashovbotirjon4

Telegram profile: t.me/Talant_Dev